=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 31=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 31 =
Mr. Liu.
السيد.  ليو.
I can explain.
أستطيع أن أشرح.
Enough.
كافية.
I can wait for half a year
يمكنني الانتظار لمدة نصف عام
as long as Lili can be cured.
طالما يمكن علاج ليلى.
Also,
ايضا،
the herbs must be
يجب أن تكون الأعشاب
boiled to perfection.
مسلوق إلى حد الكمال.
It must be supervised by a pharmacologist.
يجب أن يشرف عليها صيدلاني.
I think
أظن
Ms. Tang Qizi should be
ينبغي أن تكون السيدة تانغ Qizi
in charge of this.
المسؤول عن هذا.
Naturally,
بطبيعة الحال،
the medication charge
تهمة الدواء
is not cheap.
ليست رخيصة.
Just name the price.
ما عليك سوى تسمية السعر.
Previously, I charged the imperial...
في السابق ، قمت بتوجيه الاتهام إلى الإمبراطور ...
Based on the price of my previous consultations,
بناءً على سعر استشاراتي السابقة ،
one session
جلسة واحدة
would cost about 700 liang of silver,
سيكلف حوالي 700 ليانغ من الفضة ،
plus the cost of herbs,
بالإضافة إلى تكلفة الأعشاب ،
which amounts to 2.4 million.
والتي تصل إلى 2.4 مليون.
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك.
How much does the clinic owe you?
كم تدين لك العيادة؟
Two million whole.
مليوني كامل.
Perfect.
في احسن الاحوال.
That is worth one year of treatment.
هذا يستحق عام واحد من العلاج.
You should be able to afford it.
يجب أن تكون قادرًا على تحملها.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Money is not a problem.
المال ليس مشكلة.
Well then,
حسنا اذن،
we have other patients waiting.
لدينا مرضى آخرون ينتظرون.
So we'll take our leave.
لذلك سنأخذ إجازتنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Liu... Mr. Liu.
ليو ... السيد ليو.
Qi.
تشى.
Let's talk.
لنتحدث.
What now?
ماذا الان؟
Qizi.
بنت.
I did all this because of you.
فعلت كل هذا بسببك.
We were childhood friends for so many years.
كنا أصدقاء الطفولة لسنوات عديدة.
I couldn't bear to see you with someone else.
لم أستطع تحمل رؤيتك مع شخص آخر.
I'm just a pawn for you.
أنا مجرد بيدق لك.
You are trying to use me to acquire the clinic
أنت تحاول استخدامي للحصول على العيادة
and fulfil your greed.
وإشباع جشعك.
No.
رقم.
Qizi, I...
قيزي أنا ...
Stop lying.
كف عن الكذب.
I should have been more alert
كان يجب أن أكون أكثر يقظة
when Caichen first advised me.
عندما نصحني كايتشن لأول مرة.
Tang Qizi.
تانغ كيزي.
Don't forget.
لا تنسى.
He is your ancestor.
هو سلفك.
I haven't settled the score with you
أنا لم أحسم النتيجة معك
about the forgery of the treatise.
حول تزوير الأطروحة.
Here's a little advice for you.
إليك نصيحة صغيرة لك.
Calamity will befall those
مصيبة ستحل بهؤلاء
who are lacking in virtue.
الذين ينقصهم الفضيلة.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
So you really aren't my ancestor?
إذن أنت لست جدي حقاً؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
It all came back to me
كل هذا عاد إلي
after I returned to the painting.
بعد أن عدت إلى اللوحة.
I moved into Tang's residence
انتقلت إلى مقر إقامة تانغ
with my adoptive father
مع والدي بالتبني
and was later accepted
وتم قبوله لاحقًا
to be part of the Tang family
لتكون جزءًا من عائلة تانغ
after becoming an official.
بعد أن أصبح مسؤولاً.
As for the portrait,
أما بالنسبة للصورة ،
I think it was painted by
أعتقد أنه تم رسمه بواسطة
the Tang family's painter later on.
رسام عائلة تانغ لاحقًا.
But I have to say,
لكن علي أن أقول ،
the portrait really doesn't look anything like you.
الصورة لا تشبهك حقًا.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Yes.
نعم.
If you were not originally from the Tang family,
إذا لم تكن في الأصل من عائلة تانغ ،
then where were you from?
اذن من اين كنت
My family name is Song.
اسم عائلتي هو سونغ.
Song Qinjian?
أغنية Qinjian؟
Yes.
نعم.
[*send an invitation]
Song Qinjian؟ [* أرسل دعوة]
Song Qinjian.
سونغ كينجيان.
What's so funny?
ما المضحك في ذلك؟
I just think
فقط افكر
your name is quite
اسمك تماما
interesting.
مثير للإعجاب.
Although I am not your ancestor,
على الرغم من أنني لست أسلافك ،
I'm still your senior.
ما زلت أكبر سنك.
So, please
إذن من فضلك
show some respect.
اظهر بعض الاحترام.
Yes,
نعم،
senior.
أول.
This time
هذا الوقت
Tang deserves the most credit
يستحق تانغ أكبر قدر من التقدير
for what happened to our clinic.
لما حدث لعيادتنا.
I have only myself
لدي فقط نفسي
to blame.
إلقاء اللوم.
Father, don't say that.
أبي ، لا تقل ذلك.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
let's celebrate the comeback of our clinic.
دعونا نحتفل بعودة عيادتنا.
Father is right.
الأب على حق.
Caichen deserves the biggest credit.
يستحق Caichen أكبر تقدير.
Here's to you.
تستخدم لتمني الصحة أو النجاح لشخص قبل الشرب.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Qi.
تشى.
I have decided that
لقد قررت ذلك
from tomorrow onwards,
من الغد فصاعدا ،
you and I will take turns to sit in the clinic.
أنا وأنت سوف نتناوب على الجلوس في العيادة.
Tomorrow you go first.
غدا تذهب أولا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Tomorrow,
الغد،
Qizi would probably not be free.
ربما لن يكون Qizi حراً.
To be honest,
صدقا،
I only have 12 days left.
لم يتبق لي سوى 12 يومًا.
So,
لذا،
for the rest of the days,
لبقية الأيام ،
I don't want to be separated from Qizi.
لا أريد الانفصال عن Qizi.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض